Wallen, Saul Papers 5012
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Ford Motor Co. (Misc. 1965) - Fur Guild of New England, 8/24/51 (Box 96)
  - The Umpire: Ford Motor Company and UAW (CIO) - pg. 1-240 (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - The Umpire: Ford Motor Company and UAW (CIO) - Opinion No. B-1--B-25 (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - FMC Corporation, SO Charleston, West Virginia, and Local 348 (1 of 2), 1967 (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - FMC Corporation, SO Charleston, West Virginia and Local 348 (2 of 2), 1967 (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - Local 348 v. Food Machinery Corporation - Union Post-Hearing Brief, 1967 (Box 96, Folder 6)
  - Local 348 v. Food Machinery Corporation - Union Preliminary Brief (Box 96, Folder 7)
  - Food Machinery Corporation v. Local 348 - Transcript pgs. 1-452 (Box 96, Folder 8)
  - Food Machinery Corporation v. Local 348 - Transcript pg. 453-658, 1967 (Box 96, Folder 9)
  - Food Machinery Corporation v. Local 348 - Grievances 7332 and 7333 (Janet Surface) (Box 96, Folder 10)
  - Worker Charts: Rehire Dates in October 1966 (Box 96, Folder 11)
  - Franklin Yarn Company and Textile Workers Union of America (2/14/49), 1949 (Box 96, Folder 12)
  - Freeman Fidelity Tanning Company v. Leather Workers International Local 21, 1956 (Box 96, Folder 13)
  - Full Fashioned Hosiery Mergers and American Federation of Hosiery Workers, 1946 (Box 96, Folder 14)
  - Fur Guild of New England v. International Fur and Leather Workers Union (Box 96, Folder 15)
- G & D Mfg. Co., 8/27/59 - General Electric Co. (Pittsfield, Mass.) 11/18/1968 (Box 97)
  - G and D Manufacturing Company and International Association of Machinists, 1959 (Box 97, Folder 1)
    August 27, 1959
  - Geigy Chemical Corporation (Alrose Chemical Company Division), Cranston, Rhode Island, 1958 (Box 97, Folder 2)
    August 18, 1958
  - Geigy Chemical Corporation (Alrose Chemical Company Division), Ardsley, New York, and United Textile Workers of America, 1959 (Box 97, Folder 3)
    March 10, 1959
  - Geigy Chemical Corporation (Alrose Chemical Division), Cranston, Rhode Island, and United Textile Workers of America, 1959 (Box 97, Folder 4)
    November 24, 1959
  - Geigy Chemical Corporation (Alrose Chemical Division), Cranston, Rhode Island, and United Textile Workers of America, Local 2548, 1959 (Box 97, Folder 5)
    October 29, 1959
  - Geigy Chemical Company, Cranston, Rhode Island, and United Textile Workers of America, Local 2548, 1960 (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - Geigy Chemical Company, Cranston, Rhode Island, and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America, 1960 (Box 97, Folder 7)
    October 29, 1960
  - Geigy Chemical Company, Cranston, Rhode Island, and United Steelworkers of America, Local 2548, 1960 (Box 97, Folder 8)
  - Geigy Chemical Company, Cranston, Rhode Island, and United Textile Workers of America, Local 2548, 1960 (Box 97, Folder 9)
    November 1, 1960
  - Geigy Chemical Corporation, Cranston, Rhode Island, and United Textile Workers of America, Local 2548, 1961 (Box 97, Folder 10)
    May 12, 1961
  - Geilich Tanning Company, 1946 (Box 97, Folder 11)
    August 2, 1946
  - Geilich Tanning Company, Taunton, Massachusetts, and Taunton Leather Workers Union, 1948 (Box 97, Folder 12)
    December 22, 1948
  - Gem Crib and Cradle Company, and United Furniture Workers of America, Local 154, 1951 (Box 97, Folder 13)
    August 30, 1951
  - General Cable Corporation, and Local 331 of the United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America, 1953 (Box 97, Folder 14)
    November 12, 1953
  - General Cable Corporation, and Local 331 of the United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America, 1953 (Box 97, Folder 15)
  - General Cable Corporation, and Local 331 of the United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America, 1953 (Box 97, Folder 16)
  - General Cable Corporation, and Local 331 of the United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America, 1953 (Box 97, Folder 17)
    November 13, 1953
  - General Cable Corporation, and Local 331 of the United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America, 1953 (Box 97, Folder 18)
    November 16, 1953
  - General Cable Corporation, and Local 331 of the United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America, 1953 (Box 97, Folder 19)
  - General Cable Corporation, and Local 331 of the United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America, 1955 (Box 97, Folder 20)
    January 3, 1955
  - General Cable Corporation, and Local 331 of the United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America, 1955 (Box 97, Folder 21)
  - General Cable Corporation, and Local 331 of the United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America, 1955 (Box 97, Folder 22)
  - General Cable Corporation, and Local 331 of the United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America, 1955 (Box 97, Folder 23)
  - General Cable Corporation, and Local 331 of the United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America, 1955 (Box 97, Folder 24)
  - General Cable Corporation, and Local 331 of the United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America, 1955 (Box 97, Folder 25)
  - General Cable Corporation, and Local 331 of the United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America, 1955 (Box 97, Folder 26)
    January 31, 1955
  - General Cable Corporation, and Local 331 of the United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America, 1955 (Box 97, Folder 27)
    February 21, 1955
  - General Cable Corporation, and Local 331 of the United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America, 1955 (Box 97, Folder 28)
  - General Cable Corporation, and Local 331 of the United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America, 1955 (Box 97, Folder 29)
    February 22, 1955
  - General Cable Corporation, and Local 331 of the United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America, 1955 (Box 97, Folder 30)
    February 23, 1955
  - General Cable Corporation, and Local 331 of the United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America, 1955 (Box 97, Folder 31)
  - General Cable Corporation, and International Association of Machinists, Lodge 2101, 1957 (Box 97, Folder 32)
    June 31, 1957
  - General Cable Corporation, and International Association of Machinists, Lodge 2101, 1957 (Box 97, Folder 33)
    June 3, 1957
  - General Cable Corporation, and International Association of Machinists, Lodge 2101, 1957 (Box 97, Folder 34)
  - General Cable Corporation, and International Association of Machinists, Lodge 2101, 1957 (Box 97, Folder 35)
    June 4, 1957
  - General Cable Corporation, and International Association of Machinists, Lodge 2101, 1957 (Box 97, Folder 36)
  - General Cable Corporation, and International Association of Machinists, Lodge 2101, 1957 (Box 97, Folder 37)
    June 5, 1957
  - General Cable Corporation, and International Association of Machinists, 1957 (Box 97, Folder 38)
  - General Cable Corporation, and International Association of Machinists, 1957 (Box 97, Folder 39)
    July 31, 1957
  - General Cable Corporation, and International Association of Machinists, 1957 (Box 97, Folder 40)
    July 30, 1957
  - General Cable Corporation, and International Association of Machinists, 1957 (Box 97, Folder 41)
  - General Cable Corporation, and International Association of Machinists, 1957 (Box 97, Folder 42)
    July 11, 1957
  - General Cable Corporation, and International Association of Machinists, 1957 (Box 97, Folder 43)
    September 11, 1957
  - General Cable Corporation, and International Association of Machinists, 1957 (Box 97, Folder 44)
  - General Cable Corporation, and International Association of Machinists, Lodge 2101, 1957 (Box 97, Folder 45)
    November 1, 1957
  - General Cable Corporation, and International Association of Machinists, Lodge 2101, 1957 (Box 97, Folder 46)
    November 2, 1957
  - General Cable Corporation, and International Association of Machinists, Lodge 2101, 1957 (Box 97, Folder 47)
    November 4, 1957
  - General Cable Corporation, and International Association of Machinists, Lodge 2101, 1957 (Box 97, Folder 48)
  - General Cable Corporation, and International Association of Machinists, 1958 (Box 97, Folder 49)
    January 23, 1958
  - General Cable Corporation, and International Association of Machinists, 1958 (Box 97, Folder 50)
  - General Cable Corporation, and International Association of Machinists, 1958 (Box 97, Folder 51)
    January 25, 1958
  - General Cable Corporation, and International Association of Machinists, 1958 (Box 97, Folder 52)
  - General Cable Corporation, and International Association of Machinists, 1958 (Box 97, Folder 53)
    January 26, 1958
  - General Cable Corporation, and International Association of Machinists, 1958 (Box 97, Folder 54)
    January 27, 1958
  - General Cable Corporation, and International Association of Machinists, 1958 (Box 97, Folder 55)
    March 3, 1958
  - General Cable Corporation, and International Association of Machinists, 1958 (Box 97, Folder 56)
    April 25, 1958
  - General Cable Corporation, and International Association of Machinists, 1958 (Box 97, Folder 57)
    April 26, 1958
  - General Cable Corporation, and International Association of Machinists, 1958 (Box 97, Folder 58)
    April 29, 1958
  - General Cable Corporation, and International Association of Machinists, Lodge 157, 1959 (Box 97, Folder 59)
    March 16, 1959
  - General Cable Corporation, and International Association of Machinists, Lodge 157, 1959 (Box 97, Folder 60)
    March 18, 1959
  - General Cable Corporation, and International Association of Machinists, Lodge 157, 1959 (Box 97, Folder 61)
  - General Cable Corporation, and International Association of Machinists, Lodge 157, 1959 (Box 97, Folder 62)
  - General Cable Corporation, and International Association of Machinists, Lodge 157, 1959 (Box 97, Folder 63)
    March 19, 1959
  - General Cable Corporation, and International Association of Machinists, Lodge 157, 1959 (Box 97, Folder 64)
  - General Cable Corporation, and International Association of Machinists, Lodge 157, 1959 (Box 97, Folder 65)
    April 16, 1959
  - General Cable Corporation, and International Association of Machinists, Lodge 2101, 1960 (Box 97, Folder 66)
    March 3, 1960
  - General Cable Corporation, and International Association of Machinists, Lodge 2101, 1960 (Box 97, Folder 67)
    April 4, 1960
  - General Cable Corporation, and International Association of Machinists, 1960 (Box 97, Folder 68)
  - General Cable Corporation, and International Association of Machinists, 1960 (Box 97, Folder 69)
    April 5, 1960
  - General Cable Corporation, and International Association of Machinists, 1960 (Box 97, Folder 70)
    April 6, 1960
  - General Cable Corporation, and International Association of Machinists, 1960 (Box 97, Folder 71)
  - General Cable Corporation, and International Association of Machinists, 1960 (Box 97, Folder 72)
    April 7, 1960
  - General Cable Corporation, and International Association of Machinists, 1960 (Box 97, Folder 73)
    April 21, 1960
  - General Cable Corporation, and International Association of Machinists, 1960 (Box 97, Folder 74)
    May 5, 1960
  - General Cable Corporation, and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 1800, 1967-1968 (Box 97, Folder 75)
  - General Electric Company, and United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America (Congress of Industrial Organizations), 1948 (Box 97, Folder 76)
    May 1948
  - General Electric Company, Schenectady, New York, and International Union of Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers, Local 301, 1957 (Box 97, Folder 77)
    July 27, 1957
  - General Electric Company, West Lynn, Massachusetts, and American Federation of Technical Engineers, 1959 (Box 97, Folder 78)
    February 16, 1959
  - General Electric Company, Schenectady, New York, and International Union of Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers, Local 301, 1967 (Box 97, Folder 79)
    June 29, 1967
  - General Electric Company, Pittsfield, Massachusetts, and the International Union of Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers Local 255, 1968 (Box 97, Folder 80)
    April 11, 1968
- General Foods, 10/8/53 - General Seafoods Corp., 9/28/53 (Box 98)
  - General Foods Corp., Birdseye Div. and Atlantic Fishermen's Union, 1954 (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Insulated Wire Works, In c. Div. General Cable Corps. (and) International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local 1242 Case L 31405, 1961 (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - General Leather Finishing Co.,Inc. Salem Mass. (and) Leather Workers I.U., Local 21, 1964 (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - General Motors Corporation GMC Truck and Coach Div. -and- International Association of Machinists, 1951 (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - General Motors Corps. Frigidaire Division Dayton, Ohio (and) International Union IUE AFL-CIO, 1960 (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - General Motors Corps. Frigidaire Division Dayton, Ohio (and) International Union IUE Appeal Case H-1127 Umpire Case H-18, 1960 (Box 98, Folder 6)
  - General Motors Corps. Detroit, Michigan. (and), 1960 (Box 98, Folder 7)
  - General Foods Corp. - Birds Bye Div. and Atlantic Fishermen's Un., AFL, 1953 (Box 98, Folder 8)
  - General Motors Corpn. Detroit, Michigan (and) International, IUE - AFL-CIO, 1960 (Box 98, Folder 9)
  - General Motors Corp., Packard Electric Women, Ohio and I.U.Electrical Workers, 1960 (Box 98, Folder 10)
  - General Motors Corpn. Frigidaire Div. Dayton, Ohio (and) I.U.E. Appeal Decision H-917 Umpire Case H-17, 1960 (Box 98, Folder 11)
  - General Motors Corps. Frigidaire Division Dayton, Ohio (and) International Union IUE Appeal Case H-2104 Umpire Case H-21, 1960 (Box 98, Folder 12)
  - General Motors Corps. Frigidaire Division Dayton, Ohio (and) International Union IUE Appeal Case H-1876 Umpire Case H-20, 1960 (Box 98, Folder 13)
  - General Motors Corps. Frigidaire Division Dayton, Ohio (and) International Union IUE Grievance A-0356 Umpire Case H-19, 1960 (Box 98, Folder 14)
  - General Motors Corps. Frigidaire Division Dayton, Ohio (and) IUE AFL-CIO Local #801 Appeal Cases, 1961 (Box 98, Folder 15)
  - General Motors Corps. Warren, Ohio (and) International Union, I.U.E. AFL-CIO, 1961 (Box 98, Folder 16)
  - General Motors Corps. Frigidaire Division Dayton, Ohio (and) IUE Local 801 Appeal H-1703 Umpire Case H-26, 1961 (Box 98, Folder 17)
  - General Motors Corpn. Dayton, Ohio (Delco) (and) I.U.E. AFL-CIO Umpire Case H-30, 1961 (Box 98, Folder 18)
  - General Motors Corps. Frigidaire Division Dayton, Ohio (and) IUE Umpire Case H-35 Appeal Case H-4124 Griev. 81053-A, 1961 (Box 98, Folder 19)
  - General Motors Corps. Frigidaire Division Dayton, Ohio, 1961 (Box 98, Folder 20)
  - General Motors Corps. Frigidaire Division Dayton, Ohio (and) IUE Umpire Case H-33 Appeal Case H-417 Griev. No. 64751-A, 1961 (Box 98, Folder 21)
  - General Motors Corps. Frigidaire Division Dayton, Ohio, 1962 (Box 98, Folder 22)
  - General Motors Corps. Frigidaire Div. Dayton, Ohio (and) I.U.E. Umpire Case H-34 Appeal Case 1610 Griev. 71133A, 1962 (Box 98, Folder 23)
  - General Motors Corpn. Frigidaire Division, Dayton, Ohio (and) International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers Local #801, Decision J-4 Appeal Case J-142, 1962 (Box 98, Folder 24)
  - General Motors Corpn. Frigidaire Div. Dayton, Ohio (and) International Union of Electrical Radio and Machine Workers Dec. J-5 Umpire Appeal Case, 1962 (Box 98, Folder 25)
  - General Motors Corpn. Frigidaire Div. Dayton, Ohio (and) International Union of Electrical Radio and Machine Workers Local #801 Decision J-2 Appeal Case J-124, 1962 (Box 98, Folder 26)
  - General Motors Corpn. Frigidaire Div. (and) International of Electrical Workers Umpire Case J-8 Appeal J-376, 1963 (Box 98, Folder 27)
  - General Motors Corporation Delco Remy Division New Brunswick, New Jersey, 1963 (Box 98, Folder 28)
  - General Motors Corporation Frigidaire Division Dayton, Ohio (and) I.U.E. Local 801, 1963 (Box 98, Folder 29)
  - General Motors Corpn. Frigidaire Division, Dayton, Ohio (and) I.U.E., 1963 (Box 98, Folder 30)
  - General Motors Frigidaire Div. and I.U.E. Local 801, 1966 (Box 98, Folder 31)
  - General Motors Frigidaire Div. and I.U.E. Local 801 K-2, 1966 (Box 98, Folder 32)
  - General Seafoods Corp. -- "Drift" and Atlantic Fishermen's Un., AFL, 1953 (Box 98, Folder 33)
- General Tire & Rubber Co., 5/17/48 - 1/27/54 (Box 99)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company Past Arbitration Awards, 1948 (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company 1949 (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company Grievance #3658, 1949 (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company Grievance #2710, 1949 (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company Grievance #2109, 1949 (Box 99, Folder 5)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company Grievance #3954, 1949 (Box 99, Folder 6)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company Grievance #3868, 1949 (Box 99, Folder 7)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company Grievance #3874, 1949 (Box 99, Folder 8)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company Grievance #3403, 1949 (Box 99, Folder 9)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company Grievance #3879-1428-2237, 1949 (Box 99, Folder 10)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company Grievance #3886, 1949 (Box 99, Folder 11)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company Grievance #3406, 1949 (Box 99, Folder 12)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company Grievance #3451, 1949 (Box 99, Folder 13)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company Akron, Ohio -and- United Rubber Workers of America-CIO, 1949 (Box 99, Folder 14)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company Akron, Ohio -and- United Rubber Workers of America-CIO, 1949 (Box 99, Folder 15)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company Akron, Ohio -and- United Rubber Workers of America-CIO, 1949 (Box 99, Folder 16)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company Grievance #4054, 1949 (Box 99, Folder 17)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company Grievance #4459, 1949 (Box 99, Folder 18)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company Grievance #4063, 1949 (Box 99, Folder 19)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company Grievance #4064, 1949 (Box 99, Folder 20)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company Grievance #4062, 1949 (Box 99, Folder 21)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company Grievance #4056, 1949 (Box 99, Folder 22)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company Akron, Ohio -and- URCL and PWA - CIO, 1949 (Box 99, Folder 23)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company Akron, Ohio -and- URCL and PWA - CIO, 1949 (Box 99, Folder 24)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company Grievance #4074, 1950 (Box 99, Folder 25)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company Grievance #4082, 1950 (Box 99, Folder 26)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company Grievance #4083, 1950 (Box 99, Folder 27)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company Grievance #4308, 1950 (Box 99, Folder 28)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company Grievance #4081, 1950 (Box 99, Folder 29)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company Grievance #3223, 1950 (Box 99, Folder 30)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company Grievance #4078, 1950 (Box 99, Folder 31)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company Grievance #4302, 1950 (Box 99, Folder 32)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company -and- URCL and PWA - Local 312, 1951 (Box 99, Folder 33)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company -and- URCL and PWA - Local 9, 1951 (Box 99, Folder 34)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company -and- URCL and PWA - Local 312, 1952 (Box 99, Folder 35)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company -and- URCL and PWA - Local 312, 1952 (Box 99, Folder 36)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company -and- URCL and PWA - Local 9, 1952 (Box 99, Folder 37)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company -and- URCL and PWA - Local 9, 1952 (Box 99, Folder 38)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company -and- URCL and PWA - Local 312, 1952 (Box 99, Folder 39)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company -and- URCL and PWA - Local 312, 1952 (Box 99, Folder 40)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company -and- URCL and PWA - Local 312, CIO, 1952 (Box 99, Folder 41)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company -and- URCL and PWA - Local 312- CIO, 1952 (Box 99, Folder 42)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company -and- URCL and PWA - Local 312 Dec. No. W-33, 1952 (Box 99, Folder 43)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company -and- URCL and PWA - Local 312 Decis. No. W-34, 1952 (Box 99, Folder 44)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company -and- URCL and PWA - Local 312 W-35, 1952 (Box 99, Folder 45)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company -and- URCL and PWA - Local 312 Dec. No. W-51, 1953 (Box 99, Folder 46)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company -and- URCL and PWA - Local 312 Decis. No. W-36, 1953 (Box 99, Folder 47)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company -and- URCL and PWA - Local 312 Decis. No. W-37, 1953 (Box 99, Folder 48)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company -and- URCL and PWA - Local 312 Decis. No. W-38, 1953 (Box 99, Folder 49)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company -and- URCL and PWA - Local 312 Decis. No. W-39, 1953 (Box 99, Folder 50)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company -and- URCL and PWA - Local 9, 1953 (Box 99, Folder 51)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company -and- URCL and PWA - Local 9, 1953 (Box 99, Folder 52)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company -and- URCL and PWA - Local 9, 1953 (Box 99, Folder 53)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company -and- URCL and PWA, CIO - Local 312, 1953 (Box 99, Folder 54)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company -and- URCL and PWA, CIO- Local 312, 1953 (Box 99, Folder 55)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company -and- URCL and PWA, CIO- Local 312, 1953 (Box 99, Folder 56)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company -and- URCL and PWA - Local 312, 1953 (Box 99, Folder 57)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company -and- URCL and PWA - Local 312, 1953 (Box 99, Folder 58)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company -and- URCL and PWA - Local 312, 1953 (Box 99, Folder 59)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company -and- URCL and PWA - Local 312, 1953 (Box 99, Folder 60)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company -and- URCL and PWA - Local 9 Decision - A14 Pet. No. 3181, 1954 (Box 99, Folder 61)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company -and- URCL and PWA - Local 9 Akron, Ohio Decision A13 Pet. No. 3951, 1954 (Box 99, Folder 62)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company -and- URCL and PWA - Local 9 Akron, Ohio Decision A12 Pet. No. 3013, 1954 (Box 99, Folder 63)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company -and- URCL and PWA - Local 312, 1954 (Box 99, Folder 64)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company -and- URCL and PWA - Local 312, 1954 (Box 99, Folder 65)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company -and- URCL and PWA - Local 312, 1954 (Box 99, Folder 66)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company -and- URCL and PWA - Local 312, 1954 (Box 99, Folder 67)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company -and- URCL and PWA - Local 312, 1954 (Box 99, Folder 68)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company -and- URCL and PWA - Local 312, 1954 (Box 99, Folder 69)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company -and- URCL and PWA - Local 312, 1954 (Box 99, Folder 70)
- General Tire & Rubber Co., (Wako, Tex.), 6/15/55 - 12/22/58 (Box 100)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company -and- URCL and PWA - Local 312 W-59, 1955 (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company -and- URCL and PWA - Local 312 Grievance W-60, 1955 (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company -and- URCL and PWA - Local 312 Grievance 61, 1955 (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company -and- URCL and PWA - Local 312, 1955 (Box 100, Folder 4)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company -and- URCL and PWA - Local 312 Grievance 6662, 1955 (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company -and- URCL and PWA - Grievance 6316, 1955 (Box 100, Folder 6)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company -and- URCL and PWA -, 1955 (Box 100, Folder 7)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company -and- URCL and PWA - Grievance 6453, 1955 (Box 100, Folder 8)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company -and- URCL and PWA - W-69, 1955 (Box 100, Folder 9)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company -and- URCL and PWA -, 1955 (Box 100, Folder 10)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company -and- URCL and PWA - Local 312, 1955 (Box 100, Folder 11)
  - General Tire and Rubber Company -and- URCL and PWA - Local 312, 1955 (Box 100, Folder 12)